re-quest.net 2016-01-26

# Privacy Policy @ Re-QUEST dot Net (tm)

     Because Internet user privacy and confidentiality is of the utmost concern and importance to us at **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™, we openly volunteer our practice of collecting information, our targeting capabilities, and our use of cookies. Our reputation and integrity as a premier Internet reference resource is directly related to how we serve the Internet community. Below please find a description of how **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ is committed to safeguarding your privacy while at the same time setting standards by which others will hopefully follow thereby preserving the Internet as a credible medium for future generations to come. 

     Please read the following policy to understand how any personal information that you may provide to **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ will be treated. 

This Privacy Policy covers, the following:  
 
  1. What personal information does Re-QUEST dot Net™ collect from me?  
  2. What are cookies and how does Re-QUEST dot Net™ use them?  
  3. What is Behavorial Targeting and how is it used?  
  4. Who is collecting my information?  
  5. How is my information being used?  
  6. Who are you sharing my information with?  
  7. What choices do I have regarding the collection, use and distribution of my information?  
  8. What kind of security precautions does Re-QUEST dot Net™ take to protect my information from misuse?  
  9. How Re-QUEST dot Net™ serves to protect children's privacy.  
  10. What else should I know about online privacy?
  11. Contact us with your privacy concerns.

* * *

**1.  What personal information does Re-QUEST dot Net™ collect from me?**

     Because we value our privacy as much as you do yours, **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ _does not_ actively collect any personally identifyable information from you, except that information which is disclosed in Items 2 and 3 below and in those instances such information is collected only in the aggregate. 

     From time-to-time we may also place an occasional survey or questionnaire on our site which you are always free to participate. However, by voluntarily completing one of these surveys or questionnaires you will help us better serve you. Wherever a survey or questionnaire asks you for personal information, we always make every effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy. **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ does not sell or rent such personal information to anyone. 

* * *

**2.  What are cookies and how does Re-QUEST dot Net™ use them?**

     **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ may use cookies to improve your web browsing experience. For example, when you are first served an advertisement from **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™, we may assign a unique random ID to your computer's web browser, this process is commonly referred to in cyberspace as a "[cookie](http://www.netlingo.com/lookup.cfm?term=cookie)." We do this to understand the way you respond to the advertisments we deliver. For example, this ID lets us keep track of how many times you view an advertisement that we distribute. Likewise, the cookie can help rotate our advertisements, giving you the opportunity to see a variety of advertisments rather than the same advertisement over and over again, thus, enhancing your online web viewing experience and making our Web site more profitable at the same time. 

     From time-to-time, we may also use cookies to: 

(1)    _Estimate Our Audience Size_. Each browser accessing **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ may be given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent and duration of a visitor's usage. 

(2)    _Measure Traffic Patterns_. In measuring certain traffic patterns of **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ we are able to determine which sections of **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ you have visited and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. With this information we are better able to expand those sections of **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ which are most often utilized by our visitors and give more detail to the ones which are least visited. 

(3)    _Third Party Measurement Services_. On occasion, some of our advertisers will employ a third-party measurement service for the tracking and performance of a particular advertising campaign. In these instances, **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ has no control over the information being collected by the third party and, therefore, we may not be held responsible for the actions of the third party where such collected information is concerned. If you have any questions regarding a specific third party measurement service and their respective method of information collection, please contact us. 

     **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ may also from time-to-time collect [IP addresses](http://www.netlingo.com/lookup.cfm?term=IP+address) for use in system auditing and administration and, in some instances, we may report such aggregate information to our advertisers, sponsors, affiliates and/or partners. 

* * *

**3.  What is Behavorial Targeting and how is it used?**

     **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ uses many third-party advertising companies who help us serve the ads which appear on our website. By visiting **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ as well as other websites, these third-party companies may use your web surfing habits on an aggregated basis (which does NOT include your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that might be of interest to you, as opposed to just showing you random advertisements. Because your behavior, i.e., your recent web surfing habits, these advertisements are targeted towards those areas of interest. For instance, if you recently visited several pet websites, you might see pet related advertisements. Hence, in the Internet advertising community, this is known as "Behavorial Targeting." 

     If you would like more information about this practice and want to know more about your choices of whether or not to allow this information to be used by these third-party companies, you may visit the [NetworkAdvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) website and choose to opt-out of behavorial targeting. 

     **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ does not do any behavorial targeting of its own. 

* * *

**4.  Who is collecting my information?**

     Should you happen to voluntarily complete our demographic survey, rest assured any personal information obtained via the survey, i.e. age, occupation, etc., will only be used to make our website a better experience for future vistors. Such information may from time to time be collected by third parties but only collected in the aggregate. By knowing our vistiors' demographics, you are helping us expand those areas of interest which attract the most visitor attention. 

     **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ is involved in several affiliate programs. These programs are conducted by reputable companies that have separate privacy polices and data collection practices. **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies. For more information regarding these affiliate programs and their privacy policies, please visit these affiliate sites and review their separate policy regarding your privacy. 

     We have painstakeningly visited, reviewed and eliminated web sites from our directory which we feel are malicious or which exist solely to collect personal information from you, usually to sell or trade to others. Nothwithstanding this effort, you should be aware that **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ does contain links to a few web sites that may collect some personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those web sites are not covered under this Privacy Policy. Please consult these Websites for their own privacy policy to understand how they may treat your personal information. 

* * *

**5.  How is my information being used?**

     Currently, no personally identifiable information is being used by **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™, except for survey results (see Section 4, Paragraph 1 above) and in those instances such information is only used in the aggregate. 

* * *

**6.  Who are you sharing my information with?**

     **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ does not disclose any personally identifiable information about you except when we have your permission or under special circumstances. Some special circumstances may include, but are not limited to, the following: 

(1)    _Aggregated User Statistics_. **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ may disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, frequency of visits, demographics, survey results, etc.) in order to best describe our services and visitor base to prospective advertisers, affiliates and/or partners. 

(2)    _Other Lawful Instances_. **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to, or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with, our rights or property, other **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ may also disclose such user information when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires it. 

* * *

**7.  What choices do I have regarding the collection, use and distribution of my information?**

     Because we strongly believe in your right to privacy, we take this time to alert you to the several choices you have with respect to cookies. By modifying your web browser's preferences, you have the ability to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is about to be set, or to reject cookies altogether. Please consult your web browser's help section for more information on how to change your viewing preferences. Because we honor your right to privacy, should you choose to set your web browser preferences to reject all cookies, your visit to **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ will not be impaired. 

     Rest assured that **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ does not sell or rent its user's information to anyone. 

* * *

**8.  What kind of security precautions does Re-QUEST dot Net™ take to protect my information from misuse?**

     Unfortunately, cyberspace has not yet evolved to a realm where the Internet is a totally secure environment. Consequently, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us. However, once we are in receipt of a transmission from you, we make every effort to ensure its security while it is in our possession, custody or control, including limiting the availability of your personal information to only key **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ personnel and by storing such information offline in a secured and password protected environment. 

* * *

**9.  How does Re-QUEST dot Net™ serve to protect children's privacy?**

     The safety of children surfing the Internet is of great importantance to us at **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™. As such, **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children of any age. Notwithstanding this, children should always ask a parent for permission before sending any personal information to **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™, or to anyone else in cyberspace for that matter. **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ does not share personal information about its visitors with third parties regardless of their age, except as outlined in herein, and in those instances only in the aggregate. 

     Furthermore, while our web site was designed to be user friendly to both students and professionals, we are aware of our attractiveness to children, especially those doing homework assignments. We have, therefore, not provided any links to web sites which we believe may contain content not suitable or appropriate for children of any age. In addition, our Search Engine has been specifically designed to weed out inappropriate, lewd and sexual content. **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ will always strive to protect children from the black holes of cyberspace and we challenge other web sites to join us in this endeavor. 

     **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ has fully complied with the requirements of the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998](http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm) as well as the recommendations regarding the same as published by the [Federal Trade Commission](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/coppa.htm). In our attempt to better serve our younger audience, our actions not to seek out personally identifiable information from persons under the age of 13 without prior written permission from their parents or guardians pre-dates the concerns of Congress and the aforementioned legislative Act. Rest assured, while visiting **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™, your children will be treated as if they were our own. **Re-QUEST dot Net** ™ takes every precaution to keep our content and your children's privacy our top concern. 

* * *

**10.  What else should I know about online privacy?**

     Please keep in mind and be aware that whenever you voluntarily disclose any personal information online, _i.e._ through e-mail, usenet newsgroups, message boards or in chat arenas, such information may be collected and used by others. In essence, if you post personal information online it becomes part of the public domain and, thus, you can expect to receive some unsolicited messages and advertisements, commonly referred to in cyberspace as "[spam](http://www.netlingo.com/lookup.cfm?term=spam)." Some of these may come from less than reputable people and sources. 

     Please act responsible and be careful whenever you're online. _"Trust everyone, but brand your cattle!"_

     For more information regarding your online privacy, see also: 

Helps you surf the Internet safely and anonymously, preventing web sites from gathering personal information about you.
A civil liberties organization working to protect your rights online.
A public interest research center established to focus on civil liberties and privacy.
Information regarding protecting your privacy. [Federal Trade Commission (FTC)](http://www.ftc.gov/).
A free and small software program that empowers you to make informed decisions about your online privacy without limiting your ability to receive products and services. Find out who is watching you while you surf the Internet.
A privacy rights organization providing tips to help with unwanted and unsolicited e-mail and advertisements.
A public information program to increase awareness among parents, guardians, youngsters, and teachers about privacy on the Internet and the protections of the law. From the [Federal Trade Commission (FTC)](http://www.ftc.gov/).

* * *

**11.  Contact Information**

        Questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to:  

**Write Us :**

**Re-QUEST dot Net** ™  
Attn: Privacy Concerns  
2321 E. 4th Street  
Suite C-207  
Santa Ana, California 92705  
USA  

**Telephone :**

+1 714.264.7756  - Pacific Standard Time Zone  

**E-Mail :**

E-Mail Us
